{
    "subject": "resource/Pink_Floyd",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Capitol_Records_artists",
    "human_readable": "Pink Floyd is subject to Category: Capitol Records artists.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9800989627838135,
            "question": "Is Pink Floyd considered a Capitol Records artist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9554967880249023,
            "question": "What category does Pink Floyd belong to according to Capitol Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7999335527420044,
            "question": "How long has Pink Floyd been associated with Capitol Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7766737937927246,
            "question": "Name some artists signed to Capitol Records."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6925973892211914,
            "question": "Which record label is Pink Floyd associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4670962691307068,
            "question": "Who are some other notable musicians signed to Capitol Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4643171429634094,
            "question": "What is Capitol Records known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.385444700717926,
            "question": "What are some popular albums by Pink Floyd?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3667450249195099,
            "question": "Are there other famous bands on the same record label as Pink Floyd?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2799181640148163,
            "question": "What genre of music is Pink Floyd known for?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Pink Floyd is subject to Category: Capitol Records artists.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7304_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there other famous bands on the same record label as Pink Floyd?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7304_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular albums by Pink Floyd?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7304_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Capitol Records known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7304_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7304_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7304_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7304_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7304_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7304_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7304_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7304_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7304_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7304_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7304_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here's the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that while the documents do mention Pink Floyd, they do not indicate that the band is a subject to Category: Capitol Records artists. The documents do provide information about the band's albums, sales figures, and awards, but there is no mention of their affiliation with Capitol Records."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided context does not mention any information about Pink Floyd being associated with the Capitol Records label or falling under a specific category related to that record label. Therefore, based on the given documents, the statement is not supported and hence the answer is \"no\"."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}